Lisbon. Lisbon!
Don't move.
Does it bite?
He could've killed me.
- CBI?
- Yes, Sir. Lisbon. Jane.
Mullery. What took you so long?
Sheriff, I understand this
is a tough situation for you.
Tough situation?
This is deputy Nelson Capel.
Been with me 15 years. Got 3 kids.
He answered a 9-1-1 call last night
at 10:23 from a local girl
Keeley Farlowe, on her cell phone.
She gave her location here,
and the line went dead.
This is deputy Lance Connor.
Five years in.
His dad was in high school with me.
The E. M. T. captain you see
there crying like a baby
that's my nephew Todd.
The reason he's crying, Keeley,
that's his fiancée, throat cut.
So, yeah, tough situation.
You go ahead and look at whatever
it is you wanna look at.
Let me know when you're done, so we
can take these folks someplace decent.
Yeesh. This is trouble.
Interesting, though.
Three different methods of killing.
Why is that?
It's always bad when local cops
are personally involved.
Think the feds would want this one?
The bodies have been arranged as
well, not in an ostentatious way
but there's a definite
aesthetic at work here.
He took his time.
Yeah, it's a truly complicated maniac
we're dealing with.
- Yes. I think I will call the feds.
- No, don't do that.
I don't know why,
but I... I want this case.
Or vice versa.
All right, but I have a
feeling I'm gonna be sorry.
You people done yet?
Sheriff Mullery, just so
we're on the same page
in cases like these, we,
the CBI, have sole jurisdiction.
Your department would have
a strictly advisory role.
- That's the way...
- You can have all the jurisdiction you want.
I swear to God, the man who did this
will not live to see a courtroom.
You didn't hear that.
Yep. I'm already sorry.
- What's the password for wi-fi?
- Say?
1-2-3-4.
Of course.
So... CBI.
Top guns.
- Not really. I'm agent Grace Van Pelt.
- Bob Woolgar.
Number two around here.
That's Hobbs.
Sir, may I help you?
May I please speak with whoever is
in charge of the murder investigation?
- Why is that?
- I'm sorry. Are you in charge?
- No, but I...
- I thought not.
Sir, I'm with the CBI.
We're in charge of this investigation.
If you have any information about the
case, I'd be more than happy to help.
Miss, no offense.
You are far too young and pretty
to have any authority in the matter.
I shall wait for your chief.
"If you're media, keep movin'."
CBI. Police.
Put the weapon down right now.
All right. No problem.
No need to shout.
- And you are...
- I'm Joe Hunnicker.
Keeley's my granddaughter.
I live here with her and Todd.
Come on in.
She was a good girl.
You know, if she and Todd
hadn't brought me in here
on my V.A. check, I'd be
in a hostel somewhere.
Hey, Todd.
Lisbon. Jane.
Oh hey. Yes, we met.
Really, I-I apologize
for my outburst there.
I was, uh, a little crazy.
You can imagine.
Calmed down a little now.
Rest assured, I-I won't be
pulling any vigilante nonsense.
We're very sorry for your loss.
And I'm glad you see it that way.
There's no upside to taking
the law into your own hands.
Revenge truly doesn't work.
Well, that's just a sweeping
statement, isn't it?
I'm sure we can all think of examples
where revenge has worked splendidly.
Thanks for your input.
Just sayin'.
Tell us about Keeley.
I don't know what to say.
I love her.
We're getting married.
- We were.
- Parents?
Auto accident about five years ago.
Drunk driver.
Both dead.
When was the last time
you spoke to her?
About an hour before she was
due home... I called her and I...
I asked her to bring
home some beer and chips.
Me and Hunny were...
were playin' Gin Rummy.
And I could've picked her up.
You know, I often do when
it's raining or whatever
but last night... Last night I
was just... I was lazy, I guess.
It's basically my fault that she's dead.
Don't. Don't say that, son.
Don't take that on yourself.
Please find who did this.
I just wanna know why.
Why?
Keeley worked the late shift
for the last year.
4:00 to 10:00, as reliable as clockwork.
Great kid. Everybody loved her.
- Always had a smile for you, you know?
- Yeah, she thought the best of folks.
- Kinda naive that way.
- Meaning anyone in particular?
No, just, you know, in general, trusting.
Last night, what time
did she leave work?
10:00, as always,
on that so-and-so bicycle.
I told her it wasn't safe, but she said
it saved money and kept her skinny.
Did anything unusual happen
during her shift? Anything at all?
Not that I saw.
There was this trucker
tried to pick her up.
Come in a few times now.
Always left her, like, a 10-buck tip.
He was in here yesterday around closing
time. You remember him, Rusty?
She used to love to show her engagement
ring to guys to shut 'em down
but this guy was like, "I don't care."
He kept on trying.
- Did you get his name?
- It says "Greg" on his shirt.
You remember him
big, old, greasy fella.
Nope. Can't say I do.
He drives this truck with this
big smiling orange on the side
with arms, like, "Hi. I'm an orange."
"Examples where revenge
worked splendidly."
- Nice.
- I was just teasing.
A little hypocritical of you to lecture him
on revenge, don't you think?
How's that?
All these years you've
been helping me seek revenge?
That's different.
- How's that?
- I'm in control of the situation.
Oh, really?
She must have been abducted
somewhere along this stretch of road.
Strange we haven't found her bike.
Maybe she didn't head straight home.
What do you mean, "You're in
control of the situation"?
When the day comes,
when we find Red John
I'm gonna be there to stop you
from doing anything foolish.
We're gonna put him in
front of a judge and a jury.
- You really believe that?
- Yes, I do.
Really?
I just assumed you took that judge
and jury stuff with a grain of salt.
Well, you assumed wrong. No salt.
You know the reality will be different.
Red John is mine, and I'm gonna exact
my revenge on him.
I think, when the time comes,
you'll see that violence is not the answer.
I had no idea your naive idealism
was so deeply felt.
- Hush.
Hush.
Excuse me.
You are agent Teresa Lisbon?
- Yes, I am.
- Good evening, ma'am.
My name is Ellis Mars.
I understand you are leading the
Keeley Farlowe murder investigation.
Yes.
Poor girl.
I often saw her around
town, so fresh, innocent.
Yes?
I have information.
The killer is going to strike again.
Soon.
And how do you know that, Sir?
Well, it's hard to explain.
Some call it a third eye or E.S.P.
I think of it simply as my gift.
Not interested. Thanks, though.
Well, I've been waiting here
for several hours.
Well, perhaps you are
more broad-minded, Sir.
Uh, don't get me started.
I forgive your brusqueness. I can tell that
you have been visited by great tragedy.
Oh, really?
I'm sorry. I did not mean to offend.
I just, uh, saw it in your eyes.
Good-bye, Mr. Mars.
If you do need my help
again, please call me.
I'll happily come back.
Cho and Rigsby have gone back to
Sacramento to pick up Gregor Hobart
drives a truck for Happy Citrus Farms.
Was seen talking to Keeley
as she left work.
What about forensics?
They put a rush on the report
be here first thing in the morning
and I booked us rooms
at the nearest motel.
Reasonable price.
Deputy Hobbs says it's clean.
Good. It's been a long day.
You all right, Jane?
Oh, small-town motel, gas station
pizza. What could be better?
"Tyger, tyger."
"Tyger, tyger, burning bright."
"Tyger, tyger
In the forests of the night"
"What immortal hand or eye"
"Could frame thy fearful symmetry?"
"Symmetry?"
"Gregor Hobart?"
- Yes.
- Don't run.
- Wasn't going to.
- Yeah, you had that look about you.
No one calls me Gregor.
- What's this about?
- Keeley Farlowe.
She's dead, murdered.
Oh, no.
- You were fond of Keeley, were you?
- Yes, I was.
- Did you ever tell her that?
- Sure.
- I asked her out.
- What was her response?
Uh, I think she was intrigued.
She was engaged to be married.
We're all sinners, brother,
even nice girls like Keeley.
- And when did you last speak to her?
- Yesterday, uh, when she left work.
When she left work? Where?
Outside the diner, in the street.
She was unlocking her bike.
That makes you the last person
to see her alive.
- Apart from her killer.
- Right. So you said hi?
I said "hi." She said "hi."
She was upset
and so I tried to make her feel better.
I told her a joke.
- This goat walks into a bar...
- What was she upset about?
The cook at the dinner was hassling
her on the sly, grabbing at her.
You know, a secret lech.
They had a tussle just before I saw her.
So she was upset.
So anyway, I made her laugh
she rode off happy.
And that's the last you saw of her?
Yeah.
The strange thing?
When she was leaving, the moon
was coming up over the hills
and it looked like she was
riding to the moon... You know?
I was admiring how pretty she looked.
And at the same time,
it gave me a bad feeling
like an evil omen.
We hear you were harassing Keeley
Farlowe, putting your hands on her?
No.
We hear you had a fight with her
yesterday.
No.
- It's hot in here. Roll up your sleeves.
- That's okay. I'm not hot.
Look, a cat did this.
There is no cat, Rusty
and forensics will find your skin under
Keeley's fingernails, won't they?
I want a lawyer.
Leave him alone with me for ten minutes.
I'll get a confession.
That's a great idea.
That's not the way we work.
Don't worry about it, little lady.
Go yourself a latte.
Check your e-mail.
It won't take long.
Sheriff, I believe we have
some cultural differences here.
I think we'll take this gentleman
back to Sacramento
question him there, avoid friction.
Come on.
You had her at "little lady."
My aunt had a cat.
Little Charly Manson with fur.
"Percy" he was called.
Get it?
Purr... See. Interesting anecdote.
Just trying to keep our
friend at ease, right?
- Hey! Hey!
- I'll kill you!
Relax, Sir.
Relax and the pain will stop.
Tell me why I shouldn't charge
Todd Johnson with assault.
- I think you should.
- But he's a good kid.
He just got carried away.
Are we gonna ruin his life
with a criminal record?
I mean, hasn't he
suffered enough already?
Vengeance is not legal.
People need to know that.
So I have justice and humanity on my side
and Lisbon has a teachable moment.
Let me talk to him.
I will persuade him to drop
the notion of revenge.
- I'll put him back on the right path.
- You think you can do that?
I know I can.
I've been there.
Okay, go do that.
And if he says the right things, and I
believe him, then he can walk away.
Yes, ma'am.
Have a seat.
You just tried to kill an innocent man.
- You're very lucky you failed.
- I didn't fail.
I mean, I wasn't thinking.
I don't know what I was doing.
- You're sure he's not the guy?
- He's not the guy. Trust me.
CBI chief wants to charge you
with assault.
- Well, I guess I got it coming to me.
- Unless... Unless...
You're willing to swear
you've learned your lesson
and you won't pursue
personal vengeance.
I can't do that, Mr. Jane.
I find who did this to...
To Keeley, I will kill him.
I can't swear to do otherwise.
Todd, you repeat what I tell you now
and I will deny every word of it.
If you truly want revenge,
you have to be hard.
You have to be dishonest
and devious and cold.
You can't let people see
what's in your heart.
Okay.
So anyhow, I'm-I'm very sorry.
I swear it will never happen again.
I'm glad to hear you say that.
And I'm glad to say that you
can walk out of here a free man.
No charges.
Thank you.
- That was all B.S., right?
- It sounded pretty sincere to me.
- I hope you know what you're doing.
- About 78% sure.
- Grace, what is it?
- The ballistics report came in.
Deputy Connor was shot
with the same 45 caliber handgun
that was used
in the Howard-Ortiz murders.
- Oh, crap.
- Howard-Ortiz murders?
Two months ago, sac P.D. officer
Jeff Ortiz
was shot dead by a passing motorist.
Then exactly one month later, C.H.P.
officer Rance Howard
was shot dead
with the same handgun.
Both incidents occurred late at night
on country roads.
Howard used to work here
before your time. Good guy.
The San Francisco office has the case.
Did you talk to 'em?
Yeah, they're sending over
a copy of the case files.
A serial killer of policemen.
Very interesting.
This is not a fascinating puzzle.
It's a media crap storm.
Okay.
San Francisco basically has nothing
on the Howard-Ortiz murders.
No forensics apart from ballistics
no witnesses, no leads.
And Rusty more was on vacation in
Florida when the first murder occurred.
Hobart's company log puts him
out of range in both instances.
So we can discard both
of them as suspects.
Well, forensics found no suspicious
D.N.A. on Keeley or the two deputies.
The tire tracks at the scene
of the crime were standard make.
Over 5 million sold in California alone.
We got nothing, basically.
Well, except, a monthly pattern,
a. 45 caliber handgun
and a grudge against the police.
- But why Keeley? She's not police.
- Why not Keeley?
He sees her riding along.
It's easy to knock her off her bike.
Now he has bait
to lure the deputies into a trap.
In any case, the killer's
gotten more elaborate.
It started with a simple drive-by.
Now we have multiple victims
staging of bodies, arson.
He's beginning to enjoy himself
spreading his wings.
I'm reading your interview
with Hobart, the poetical trucker.
He says that when Keeley
rode off, and I quote
"The moon was coming up
over the hills"
"and it looked like she was
riding to the moon, you know?"
"And I was admiring
how pretty she looked"
"and at the same time, I had a bad
feeling about it, like an evil omen."
- Moon rises in the east.
- So she was riding east.
But her route home is west of the diner.
She wasn't headed home
when she left work.
We've been looking for the abduction
site on the wrong stretch of road.
Yeah, that's Keeley's bike.
Okay. We're gonna have to
cordon off this whole area.
I'm gonna call forensics,
get some techs down here.
Where does this go?
Where-where was she headed?
About half a mile down, there's a
make-out spot that the local kids use.
After that, nothing till you get
to Gainersville, 20 miles away.
Hey, I got somethin'.
Looks like a button from a peacoat
type of thing, like sailors wear?
- Sailors and, uh, firemen.
- Firemen.
We're investigating
the orchard murders.
We need a list of all the firefighters
that weren't on duty the night before last
and anyone who was supposed to
be on duty but didn't show up.
Okay.
- You look troubled.
- No.
Yeah, actually, I mean, there was one guy
who didn't show up that night, but...
There's no way. He's-he's
not that kind of guy.
What's his name?
Kitchen.
- Ben Kitchen.
- And where can we find Mr. Kitchen?
Yo, Kitch. Get out here.
These detectives wanna talk to you.
- Okay. What'd I do?
- How'd you lose your eyebrows?
Barbecue accident, at home.
And why didn't you come into work
the night before last?
Stomach bug.
Might be it was the barbecue.
- What's this about?
- Your lack of eyebrows.
I know what she looks like.
I didn't kill her.
I was home, like I said
a million times now.
You say that, but you have no proof.
I don't need proof. You need proof.
You have a bad attitude.
- What's the matter?
- My face hurts.
You don't like policemen?
Don't love 'em.
It's nothing personal.
It's a firefighter's tradition.
Sheriff Mullery.
Hey, Lisbon, I hear you
got a suspect in custody.
Yeah. He looks pretty good for it.
- Firefighter, huh?
- Yeah. Ben Kitchen?
Yeah, I know him. All right.
Look, I'm on my way to the office now.
That's all right, Sheriff.
It's early days yet.
- "We don't even know if he..."
- Don't worry. I won't interfere.
I learned my lesson...
"Hello? Sheriff?"
"Sheriff Mullery? Hello?"
"Hello?"
Waiting for confirmation
from ballistics
but the M.E. took what looks
like a 45 slug from Mullery.
Same caliber as the previous
murders, same M.O.
So we have to assume it's the same
shooter, only a different schedule.
Three days from the last murder
instead of a month.
- Why the change?
- Because he had to kill Mullery.
Because Mullery
discovered something.
Why did Mullery keep it quiet then?
And how did the killer know
that he had discovered something?
Good questions.
Sir, I don't care what you have
to say, you're not allowed in.
Please, deputy. I am trying to help.
Hobbs, it's okay. I'll deal with him.
What brings you back here, Mr. Mars?
I'm sorry. I never caught your name.
Patrick... Jane.
Patrick.
Patrick, I don't
mean to be self-serving
but I did tell you there
would be another killing.
Yes, you did.
Poor Mullery.
Lisbon was actually on the phone
with him when he died.
Well, I suppose we owe you
an apology, but, uh...
No. No, no, no, no.
Without doubt, there can be no faith.
All I ask is that you'll listen to me now
with, uh, an open mind.
Now that you know
what I say is true.
Perhaps you could imagine
how helpful that could be to you.
Can you imagine that?
- Are you trying to hypnotize me?
- No.
Patrick, of course not.
- Felt a little weird.
- Yeah. No.
Trying is nothing.
Doing is everything, and all I'm doing
is asking for you to let me help you.
I can help you.
You can help us. Come on in.
Thank you.
Lisbon, Sheriff, you remember Mr. Mars?
- Yes.
- He can help.
- Really?
- He can?
Well, I know you're skeptical,
but please, hear him out.
I think you'll be very impressed.
I need to run to the store.
Then we should take him out to
Keeley's place to look around.
I'll be right back.
- I sense that you're upset.
- Oh, really?
Oh, yes, I see.
You were the last person to speak
with Sheriff Mullery, weren't you?
Yes.
Oh, I see you right there
when he died.
No. No.
Right there, but not there.
You were on the phone with him
when he died.
How did you know that?
A psychic?
You're kidding me.
- Come on.
- This guy's good.
- What room is that?
- It's the bathroom.
So what-what's the gag?
Because this appears to be
an absurd waste of time.
Yes, it does, doesn't it?
Wait a minute, though.
You'll enjoy the next part.
The mark of a good psychic
is the ability to improvise
to use to your advantage whatever
props might come to hand.
What is it? A tooth?
A wolf's tooth.
Where on earth would
a wolf's tooth come from?
The killer must have left it here.
It's a sign.
As a clairvoyant, a man
of clear sight, if you will
it's my opinion the killer has a
strong lycanthropic complex.
He believes he's a
werewolf or a wolf man...
"were" being an
anglo-saxon word for "man."
Hence, of course, the monthly
pattern of his crimes.
His behavior is driven
by the phases of the moon.
You're saying there's a killer out there
that turns into a wolf?
No, no, no, no.
No, I'm saying there's a killer out there
who believes he turns into a wolf
and so he is a wolf
and behaves like one.
The mind is a powerful machine.
It can create reality.
And that is all...
Now I think I know
what your game is.
Really?
I'd be very surprised if you did.
Of course. You're right.
The killer is driven
by the phases of the moon.
That is brilliant.
How did you work that out?
Simple deduction.
And the last killing didn't break
the pattern at all.
It simply initiated a
different lunar cycle.
- Exactly.
- So tonight... it's a big night, huh?
- Tonight?
- Moon's at its apogee.
I'm no astrologer, but, uh, isn't
that a highly charged moment?
It can be. It depends.
And since serial killers always
have a very strong urge
to return to the scene
of their crimes...
Yeah. Wouldn't wanna be up
in those hills tonight.
That werewolf stuff
gives me the creeps.
Well, no, it's, uh, easy to be scared
of the unknown, hmm?
- Would you excuse me?
- Well, of course.
Mr. Mars, can I get one of those?
- Here, have one of there.
- Thank you.
Sheriff Woolgar, do you have any deputies
watching over the original crime scene?
No. Why?
Well, I've been thinking
about all this wolf stuff
and it occurs to me that
it's very likely that the killer will return
to the scene of the crime.
- Why?
- Well, serial killers do, don't they?
Well, some do and some don't.
Someone that thinks they're a wolf
will almost certainly return.
Wolves always return to their kills.
They do.
I'll put some men up there.
That's smart.
Good evening. Get in.
What on earth are you doing out here?
I was waiting for the killer.
But he saw me.
He chased me.
That wasn't the killer.
That was the police
and now they probably think
you're the killer.
Oh, my God. Oh my...
- This is your fault.
- Excuse me?
How so?
Did I tell you to go out there
in the middle of the night?
No, I did not.
Uh, I'll go to the police.
I'll explain things to them.
They'll see it's a misunderstanding.
Yeah, sure, they will. They'll only keep
you locked up a couple of days.
As long as no angry cops try
to take revenge, you'll be fine.
- Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
- Don't worry. I'll help you.
We can fix this, okay?
Just trust me.
Todd. It's Jane.
Meet me at the Sheriff's office.
Lisbon. Lisbon, get dressed.
I have an excellent play in motion.
Lisbon.
What is it?
Uh, get dressed.
I have an excellent play in motion.
We're about to crack the biggest
case this area's had in a long time
and we are running out of time.
I want him flagged for arrest
at all the airports in the area.
What's happening?
They found someone?
Ask Sheriff Woolgar.
Well, then let me talk to someone
who can, for crying out loud!
- Yes, I'll wait.
- What's the rumpus?
Bob, it's okay. I promise
I won't do anything crazy.
I just wanna know.
My guys spotted Ellis Mars
creeping around the crime scene.
He ran off when challenged, left his car.
We found dried blood and a long,
dark human hair the backseat.
It's on its way to forensics now.
Ellis Mars?
That doesn't make sense.
Oh, we should have realized before.
He knew Lisbon was on the phone
with Mullery when he died.
Psychic powers, he said.
Wait. He knew that?
How could he know that?
Exactly.
He's not psychic.
He was there.
Yeah, but he...
he's been helping you guys.
It's a common psychopathic
profile, classic almost.
They seek a part in the investigation,
they seek the spotlight.
- Well, where is he now?
- We don't know.
Hey. This is acting Sheriff Woolgar,
Vineland township.
Yes.
Count to ten, then meet me outside.
Well, what the heck do I have to do
to get people at the airport?
Yes, now!
Get in.
- Where are we going?
- You'll see.
Get in.
Ellis Mars is in room 21.
Consider it a gift
from a brother in arms.
I hope someday someone
will do the same for me.
You're messing with me.
No. I'll show you.
See?
- Oh, my God.
- Go ahead.
What are you waiting for?
This guy cut Keeley's
throat and watched her die.
I... I didn't.
Don't bother lying to us, Mars. We found
Keeley's blood and hair in your car.
That's impossible!
What's going on, Todd?
I'm not gonna shoot this guy.
All that talk of revenge was just hot
air, was it? You don't have the guts.
Oh, I got the guts, all right.
- I just don't know for sure he did it.
- We have hard evidence against him.
Yes, you do, and
I don't understand that.
I guess you're framing him
for some reason, but why?
And why would you want me to kill
someone who didn't really do it?
What's your game?
Huh?
You're setting me up, aren't you?
Or I'm simply telling you
the truth, and Mars is guilty.
No.
No?
And you're sure?
Yeah, well, you're right.
Mars' only crime is
foolishness and fraud.
I set him up.
Get outta here.
What's this about?
See, the thing is, Todd
there's only one way you can
be so sure of his innocence.
It was you that killed Keeley
and Mullery and all of those cops.
You're nuts.
Oh, don't-don't bother with the song
and dance. I'm satisfied you're guilty.
You're a garden variety psychopath.
Probably been killing random
people here and there for years.
I'm not sure why you turned
on cops all of a sudden
but I'm sure you have
your good reasons.
- Your dad was a cop, right?
- Yes, he was.
He was mean to you, made
you hate policemen, maybe?
No.
He was a kind and gentle man.
Then who was it that
made you this way?
And please don't say
it was your mother.
- That'd be too cliché.
- No. My mother was a saint.
You're mistaken about me.
- Really.
- Really?
Well, let me run it down for you.
You killed Keeley because
she was getting too clingy.
She was asking too many
questions about your other life.
She bugged you.
Mullery died because he recognized that
button as yours, and he asked you about it.
You stalled him, then you
had to kill him quick.
Broke the monthly pattern, which
wasn't about the moon, of course.
Once a month, Hunnicker
got his V.A. check
goes on a binge, drinks till he
blacks out, and gives you an alibi.
How am I doing so far?
- You're very clever, Mr. Jane.
- Thank you.
I must confess, I underestimated you.
More like you
overestimated yourself, Todd.
No. You say that only because you
don't see the whole big picture.
There's a reason for
everything I've done.
- What's the big picture?
- You'll never know.
Right.
There's no big picture.
Oh, trust me.
It would blow... Your... Mind.
No firing pin. Oops.
Of course.
Cho! Rigsby!
- Drop the weapon!
- Hands on your head!
You're under arrest!
What is it?
I've changed my mind.
I wanna talk.
That's a smart move.
- But I'll only talk to Mr. Jane.
- Why is that?
We have a connection.
Maybe he doesn't want to talk to you.
Tell him I have a secret.
A secret only he will understand.
A secret, huh?
That's what he said, that you were
the only one who would understand
that you and he had a connection.
He's just trying to lend an air of mystery
to his sad little story of madness.
The case will go a lot easier
if we can get him to talk.
I have spent enough time
with that creep.
Staring into the abyss.
You know, it's not healthy.
Please?
Just hear what he has to say.
He's right downstairs
in the holding cell.
P.S.U. is starting an investigation.
They figure it's somebody getting
revenge for officer Howard.
They'll need to speak with you
later today.
Okay.
Doctor says his systems
are shutting down
that he won't regain consciousness.
Okay, then.
I'm gonna go finish up
the paperwork now.
"Tyger, tyger..."